Hello friends welcome to my channel Knowledge
Ji, there will be a bank account of the business,
if there is any liability for the business, it will be the
account of this business or of an individual, whatever it will be, then whatever
your trade name will be, you have to
keep the trade license document of that bank account, all this is fine, you will have to
keep it ready first,
after that you can apply for it, so
see if this GST has been opened then
after this I am showing you the complete procedure,
so stay with me in the video, so
see I am showing you the complete procedure, from this
portal we have to apply for new
registration, so here we have to
click here,
see what is written here, new registration has to be
given only that which will be in your form, so
I have given it here, after that you have to
give the format account number, you have to input the PAN number here,
whatever you give, you will have to write it completely, there should
not be any mistake,
everyone will have to give it, so
here after my
mobile number, I have to
click on try here,
click on the registration reference number,
this is me, you guys immediately  I am showing it practically,
see I have
shown you the entire process
here from number registration
registration
here I have shown you the train, after that you have to
show the constitution which is the business, so
click here, after that
if there is anything then you have to give the addition, if there is
not,
after that see the registration on apply today itself,
now for which reason are you registering,
that you have to show, see what is your
reason here, what is your
interested supply diabetes
date of de property
[music]
and I clicked on continue,
after the password details, here you have to change the gender,
after giving the gender, if there is a telephone number then
you will see it, if not then it will not work,
write the resignation status here, give the proper
director
P code, the P code is
that you have given, which route is
yours, if you are
doing it here then give it, otherwise you do not have to give it,
what is showing in it, to
correct the continuation,
so I am also showing you people, I am
showing you people by doing the entire practical, so
see, whatever is there, you have to
give everything here, after that if you
replace someone then you have to do that and  If you do not
keep it, no problem, you have to give the Principal Place of
Business
P-code, after that if you
keep something from here then you have to give it,
after that it will not happen
and if you do not give it then this
operation
happens in it, after that you have to give the Principal Place of
Business, so if you have the place then
you give the address, after giving all that
you will have to give all that for additional Play Store business
also, if you fill it
there, then when you
fill the business in the first place,
if you give some additional rate dems there,
if you click on it then it will
show you here and otherwise it will not do it,
after that you have to click on Goods and Services here and
see, here
if you have to give the details of one thing, the goods,
in this you have to give the
mobile number which you have given with the mobile number,
if your Aadhar card is attached, that is, if you have
added this number, then after clicking here,
see,
after writing it, click on Continue,
then the same mobile number will send you the Aadhar link,
so see, the file is showing here, it is 94%
complete, after that it will be completed,
after that click on Meri Jaan  If you do this then this
is your complete registration process, once this
process is completed then
like, share and comment on the video, don't
say no.